DOWNHILL / GRAVITY ONLY
Actual game capture | Temporary 12 degree slope | 1x playback
12 degree descent | No pushing
0.6 km/h
1.9 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
3.3 km/h
4.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
6.0 km/h
7.3 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
8.7 km/h
10.0 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
11.4 km/h
12.7 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
14.1 km/h
15.4 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
16.8 km/h
18.1 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
19.5 km/h
20.8 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
22.2 km/h
23.5 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
24.9 km/h
26.2 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
27.6 km/h
28.9 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
30.3 km/h
31.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
33.0 km/h
34.4 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
35.7 km/h
37.1 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
38.4 km/h
39.8 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
41.1 km/h
42.5 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
43.8 km/h
45.2 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
46.5 km/h
47.9 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
49.2 km/h
50.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
51.9 km/h
53.3 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
54.6 km/h
56.0 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
57.3 km/h
58.7 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
60.0 km/h
61.4 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
62.7 km/h
64.1 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
65.4 km/h
66.8 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
68.1 km/h
69.5 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
70.8 km/h
72.2 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
73.5 km/h
74.9 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
76.3 km/h
77.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
79.0 km/h
80.3 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
81.7 km/h
83.0 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
84.4 km/h
85.7 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
87.1 km/h
88.4 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
89.8 km/h
91.0 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
92.0 km/h
92.7 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
93.2 km/h
93.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
93.9 km/h
94.1 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
94.2 km/h
94.4 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
94.5 km/h
94.6 km/h
12 degree descent | No pushing
94.7 km/h